Daniel Nunes Dias



www.dndias.com



contact@dndias.com



(289) 885-2240



/danieIndias



Mississauga, ON

Skills

Network Devices



SNMP

VLAN



VPN



Windows Server 2008/2012



SEO



Java



HTML/CSS



Certifications

- CCNA R&S
- ITIL V3
- ISO/IEC 20,000
- ISO/IEC 27,002
- GREEN IT CITIZEN

IT Professional with 5+ years of experience in customer support and networks. Fast learner and objective oriented, experienced in teamwork and goals achievement. I have certifications in Cisco CCNA R&S, ISO 27,002 security and ITIL v3 IT processes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Design & SEO Analyst Digihype Media – Mississauga, ON.

Mar 2017 - June 2018

- Create website mock-ups
 - Website development using WordPress
 - Website changes to improve SEO
 - SEO analysis and reports

Network Security Analyst (co-op) Jan 2018 - Apr 2018 Royal Bank of Canada - Toronto, ON.

- Integrated a project to accredit several firewall policies, totalizing more than 18 thousand rules
- Implemented security policies
- Troubleshoot network connectivity issues

Network Analyst

Jun 2015 - Dec 2016

ATIVAS Data Center - Belo Horizonte, Brazil

- Participated in the design and implementation of several network projects, such as:
 - o VLAN Segregation
 - o Network expansion
 - o Network device replacement
- Installed and configured switches, routers, and firewalls
- Designed and implemented network security policies
- Created and configured a backup policy for the network devices
- Update network documentation
- Monitored network performance

User Support Analyst

Dec 2010 - Dec 2014

Domínio Informática - São Luís, Brazil

- Configured and maintained the company servers
- Implemented project to replace more than 300 computers
- Researched and implemented open-source solutions
- Supported more than 400 company users
- Monitored and maintained network performance

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Programmer Sheridan College. Jan 2017 - Aug 2018

Postgraduate in IT Infrastructure Management
PUC Minas – Belo Horizonte, Brazil. Mar 2015 – Oct 2016

Bachelor's Degree in Information Systems CEUMA University - São Luís, Brazil. Jan 2008 - Dec 2011